在很多原因下你可能更倾向
There's a number of reasons you'd be potentially better
将你的App分解为不同的Activity。拥有一个
off breaking your app into different activities. Having a
完整而巨大的Activity会增加你代码的复杂度，
single monolithic activity increases the complexity of your code,
使得创建和管理意图过滤更为
making the creation and management of intent filters much
艰难，也使其更难维护，测试，
harder and making it more difficult to maintain, test,
和阅读。这也增加了
and read your activity code. It also increases the
紧耦合独立组件的风险并使其
risk of tightly coupling independent components and makes it
更易于引入安全风险，如果
much more likely to introduce security risks if the
这一单一活动同时包含了敏感信息和可共享的信息就会这样。
single activity includes both sensitive information and information that's safe
好的经验是在任何
to share. A good rule of thumb is to create a
上下文切换发生的时候，都新建一个Activity。比如，在从视图切换到输入数据的过程中。
new activity whenever the context changes. For example, displaying a
显示不同种类的数据。
different kind of data, while switching from viewing to entering data.